{"componentChunkName":"component---src-pages-recruitment-js","path":"/recruitment/","result":{"data":{"siglogo":{"nodes":[{"name":"Cipher","childImageSharp":{"fixed":{"srcWebp":"/static/b81db97833a2471f2c0d2788bd2f1ae9/1f5c5/Cipher.webp"}}},{"name":"Inkheart","childImageSharp":{"fixed":{"srcWebp":"/static/1add9a0899f94cff3b382238e66f3488/1f5c5/Inkheart.webp"}}},{"name":"Medium","childImageSharp":{"fixed":{"srcWebp":"/static/8b4546e9874b59d1a8c9358ea6e08f64/1f5c5/Medium.webp"}}},{"name":"Torsion","childImageSharp":{"fixed":{"srcWebp":"/static/41d4ca1a46c88d5d445d4f469e06b2fc/1f5c5/Torsion.webp"}}},{"name":"Rovisp","childImageSharp":{"fixed":{"srcWebp":"/static/c3c40a5ac3ed0ce2afe51e782577fbb4/1f5c5/Rovisp.webp"}}}]},"sigdata":{"nodes":[{"name":"Cipher","description":"Cipher SIG brings together people interested in Computer Science and Information Technology."},{"name":"Rovisp","description":"Rovisp SIG brings together people who are passionate about Electronics and Electrical Technology."},{"name":"Torsion","description":"Torsion SIG brings together people interested in Mechanical, Civil, Chemical and Material Sciences."},{"name":"Inkheart","description":"Inkheart is our new Lit&Phil SIG for people who are passionate about literature, music etc"},{"name":"Medium","description":"Medium SIG is dedicated to people interested in Media and Marketing."}]},"site_data":{"siteMetadata":{"join":{"allow":false,"link":""}}},"rec_questions":{"nodes":[{"answer":"We plan to conduct Aptitude and Technical tests online. For the interviews, we'd shortlist you with two rounds of technical interviews and one HR after that.","question":"How would the testing happen for Core SIG's (Cipher, Rovisp, Torsion)?"},{"answer":"We plan to conduct Aptitude test and a descriptive test (we'll let you know on this). For the interviews, we'd shortlist you with a round of debate/ ex tempore and one HR after that.","question":"How would the testing happen for Inkheart and Medium?"},{"answer":"Yes. Every SIG has a different online screening test, except for the general aptitude/reasoning sections. For instance, if you want to apply for both Cipher and Rovisp, you are required to take both tests in a row.","question":"Do I need to take different recruitment tests if I want to interview for different SIGs?"},{"answer":"If you have submitted every assignment, project, report etc. that were given to you, you are eligible to be called for direct interviews without going through the hassle of screening tests. Please contact your mentors to know about your eligibility.","question":"I was a part of the IET SMP conducted during the summer. Do I need to write the recruitment test?"},{"answer":"You’re allowed to interview only for the SIG that housed your SMP. You’ll have to take the online tests for the other SIGs, if you wish to apply for them.","question":"I have successfully completed an SMP under Cipher. Am I eligible for a direct interview under Rovisp/Torsion?"},{"answer":"Our targeted numbers are around 15 per SIG. It can vary depending on various factors.","question":"How many people do you plan to recruit this year?"},{"answer":"We’re open primarily for second years. But if you make a strong case, we don’t mind taking you in. You’ll have to go through the same process as second year students though. Note that we are not open for students from final year B.Tech and other non-B.Tech programs.","question":"I’m a third year student. Am I eligible to apply?"},{"answer":"We don’t mind your branch as long as you have the expected skills. All our SIGs are open for all branches.","question":"I belong to a non-CS/IT branch. Can I still apply for Cipher SIG?"},{"answer":"We don’t care about your CGPA. A high CGPA doesn’t guarantee a place among us and a low CGPA doesn’t affect your candidacy.","question":"Does my CGPA matter in the recruitments?"},{"answer":"No you cannot.","question":"Can I take a written (pen and paper) test instead of the online test?"},{"answer":"We find the idea undesirable.","question":"I’m busy during the test slot. Is it possible to hold the test another day for me?"},{"answer":"We have three rounds of interviews.","question":"How many rounds of interviews are conducted?"},{"answer":null,"question":"What if I miss to show up for a slotted interview? Will I be given another chance?"},{"answer":"Once you are shortlisted and informed about your slot, we expect you to be there right on time or before. No exceptions to this policy are allowed.","question":null}]}},"pageContext":{}},"staticQueryHashes":["3346060996","3818438335","3886595457"]}